<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>ZIO Blog</title>
        <link>https://zio.dev/blog</link>
        <description>ZIO Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ZIO ChatBot: Your AI-Powered ZIO Guide]]></title>
            <link>https://zio.dev/blog/zio-chat-announcement</link>
            <guid>https://zio.dev/blog/zio-chat-announcement</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Introducing ZIO Chat—your AI companion for ZIO, unlocking its potential with quick assistance through the ZIO website and Discord channel.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dear ZIO Community,</p><p>We are delighted to share the exciting news of the public availability of ZIO Chat, your ultimate companion for navigating the landscape of the ZIO library and its ecosystem. </p><p>ZIO Chat is trained on the documentation of ZIO core and the entire official ecosystem. It leverages the power of Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Language Model (LLM) technology to provide swift and nearly accurate answers to all your ZIO-related questions.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="two-interfaces-for-seamless-interaction">Two Interfaces for Seamless Interaction<a href="#two-interfaces-for-seamless-interaction" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Two Interfaces for Seamless Interaction" title="Direct link to Two Interfaces for Seamless Interaction">​</a></h2><p>Discover the power of ZIO Chat, your indispensable AI companion tailored for navigating the intricacies of the ZIO. This innovative tool boasts two interfaces, each designed to provide a seamless and comprehensive interaction experience.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="1-website-interface">1. Website Interface<a href="#1-website-interface" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to 1. Website Interface" title="Direct link to 1. Website Interface">​</a></h2><p>Immerse yourself in the convenience of a pop-up chatbot window on the ZIO website and engage in more profound conversations on the dedicated page at <a href="https://chat.zio.dev" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">chat.zio.dev</a>. Whether you're a seasoned ZIO veteran or a newcomer exploring the intricacies of the library, ZIO Chat is primed and ready to assist you with its wealth of knowledge.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="2-discord-interface">2. Discord Interface<a href="#2-discord-interface" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to 2. Discord Interface" title="Direct link to 2. Discord Interface">​</a></h2><p>It's also integrated into the <a href="https://discord.gg/2ccFBr4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">ZIO Discord server</a>, ready to assist you within the familiar environment of Discord channels.</p><p>You can interact with ZIO Chat via discord in two ways:</p><ul><li><p><strong>Public Channels:</strong> Activate ZIO Chat's assistance by simply mentioning the ZIO Chat user in any channel. Pose your ZIO-related questions, and ZIO Chat will promptly respond. Encourage collaborative discussions by responding to its messages, fostering an environment of shared learning.</p></li><li><p><strong>Private Questions:</strong> For confidential queries and personalized assistance, leverage ZIO Chat's direct messaging feature. Initiate a private conversation by sending a direct message (DM) to the bot, ensuring tailored responses tailored to your unique needs.</p></li></ul><p>Join us in exploring the rich ZIO ecosystem, engage with the community, and let ZIO Chat be your companion in unlocking the full potential of the ZIO library.</p><p>The ZIO Team</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>chat bot</category>
            <category>announcement</category>
            <category>documentation</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome to The ZIO Blog]]></title>
            <link>https://zio.dev/blog/welcome-to-the-zio-blog</link>
            <guid>https://zio.dev/blog/welcome-to-the-zio-blog</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Stay Up-to-Date with ZIO and its Ecosystem!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to the ZIO Blog, your source for the latest announcements and development news on ZIO and its ecosystem. </p><p>ZIO is a powerful concurrency and functional programming library for Scala that allows you to write safe and efficient concurrent programs using purely functional programming techniques.</p><p>Our blog is dedicated to sharing our knowledge and expertise on the latest development news for ZIO and its <a href="https://zio.dev/ecosystem/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">ecosystem</a>, so that you can stay up-to-date with the latest announcements and developments in this exciting field.</p><p>We welcome your feedback and comments and look forward to building a vibrant and engaged community around ZIO and its ecosystem.</p><p>Thanks for joining us, and stay tuned for more great content!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>announcement</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>